Come on.
Let's really go around.
So that's where we're going next.
The next place we're going to.
There's a glasses shop, right?
Makoto Glasses
We are going to Makoto Opticians.
It's a reward project.
If you go to a glasses shop, you must want something, right?
I'm going to Makoto Glasses.
And they have a lot of vintage glasses.
If you're going all this way...
I'd be embarrassed to buy it myself.
So we'll play a game, and the winner buys the loser a drink.
The loser buys the winner a drink.
What's the game?
A soccer game. It's the game we're into now.
So far, Mr. Alois is winning 60% of the time.
I'm winning 40% of the games, and we're winning about 50-50 every time, and it depends on the day.
We played a game just now and I lost the ball 5-0.
If I'd bought it for myself, I wouldn't be so disgusted, I'd be happy to buy it for you
If I lose, if I lose, I'm already younger than you.
He said this, by the way.
He said it out of the blue.
I don't like it.
You don't have to do this.
What's your team's par?
3,000...
3,159.
Oh, man, seriously, Mom.
Oh, my mother.
Hey, Mom.
I've been working so hard.
Mom, are you watching?
Here we go.
Now that I've said all that...
It's a battle of the armies, so to speak.
We'll do our own commentary.
Okay, I'll go first.
Let's hear it!
Go!
Seriously, I don't talk.
Here we go.
It's all about composure.
This is all about composure.
Oh!
That's good!
There's lag, and there's lag, too, in this game.
What are you sliding for? Really, really, really!
There you go! Score one, Irons!
Yeah!
You poor thing. You want to rebop?
You want a rebop?
Well, now, this camera...
I'm gonna pretend I didn't just destroy all the data on this camera.
Shake.
Oh, no!
Go easy on him.
What? What?
You go easy on him.
What are you holding back?
You're supposed to be variety.
What are you talking about?
I said go easy on the variety.
Help! Help me!
What's that?
Here.
Can I cut off the receipt?
Ha-ha-ha.
Of course not!
Ha!
Ha ha!
Counter
Counter counter counter counter
Messy senior, seriously.
I really appreciate you.
Oh, Mr. Messy
Oh, no!
I really love you, Mr. Messy.
Mr. Messy.
Mr. Messy, Mr. Messy, nice bass.
Mr. Klyffe.
Me and Gosha are the same.
Gosh, Gosh, yes, Mr. Clife.
I'm serious.
ahahahahaha
hahahahahaha
Ha ha ha ha ha
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
hahahahahaha
Now we have a tie.
Oh, my God!
We're tied now.
I'm leaving this here.
I swear to God, man.
You're gonna pay for losing.
Because just now...
By all means, you've changed.
Oh, hey, go easy on me, man. Really, really.
Really go easy on me. Really go easy on me.
I'm serious. Gulp. Hey, bro.
Oh, brother, really go easy on me, brother.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Aah!
Ahhh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What's that?
Oh, my God, I don't know.
Uh-oh.
Offside.
This is the most exciting game I've ever seen.
How's it going?
Is it coming through?
What do you think?
Look.
Fukazawa, can you feel it? I'm nervous.
Drink up, won't you?
Oh, no, it's back to normal!
Jance was right on target.
What shall we choose? The rarest one...
I want to buy a free kick now!
I'm buying a free kick right now!
Three against one...
Where did the opposite sex go?
No...
How long is the match?
It's 12 minutes.
The first half and the second half are six minutes and six minutes.
Maybe.
But!
All right!
Yeah!
He's not talking to me.
Why are you going that way?
Yeah!
No, it's because he just started talking to me.
Okay!
If I bend this, is that the end of the book?
All right!
Yeah!
Yeah! - Yeah!
Okay. - Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
Real nice.
How's that nice?
Can you talk to me for real, for real? Seriously.
What do you mean, "nice"? I know, I know, I know.
What is it? It's so nice.
Oh, my God!
Oh, man...
Nice try.
There's a way to tell.
Over there, here.
It's important.
Three?
Nice try.
Seriously, I'm changing what I can eat tomorrow.
That's really not a good idea, is it? Senpai.
Senpai?
It's just you and me for the rest of the day.
Huh?
First half is over.
Aww...
The score is 3 to 2.
Yes, sir.
I'm the one who's lining up to take it.
What the hell are you doing?
If you're Japanese, use Japanese.
Be quiet.
Oh, no!
I'm with you.
Aww..,
Awww!
Go talk to him next.
Seriously, really, go talk to him next time.
I don't know. I'm up 3 to 2.
I'm winning the first half.
Aww...
Well, well, well...
Why are you there, senpai?
Be really nice.
What?
I'm dying
I'm dying... but he turned on the air conditioner... and the sound is great...
I know you're going to say "go", but it doesn't matter anymore.
My life depends on it.
Let's go slow.
Jerry
Jerry!
All right, all right, all right.
Earphones
Clear! Clear! Clear! Clear!
Oh, no, I don't want to talk!
Oh, I don't want to talk!
Don't talk to me!
My life depends on it tomorrow!
This!
I got this!
Wait a minute.
Let's just play a normal game.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
He's doing it.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Aah! Oh, my God!
I'm working on it.
If this doesn't work...
Boom!
I'm not going to that kind of overtime.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, who's driving?
I see... Sakao, I'll let you take your own road.
What are you doing? Why are you... you know... oh, there's so many of them!
Thank you very much.
Hey, hey, hey! Why is everyone cheering for Aloha?
You should be cheering for me too!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Just in time! He's in a hurry!
Matsuda, please stop it! Miyachika really won!
ez
Oh no, first of all, I won't do this Enchou Arius!
identified
A-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, I'm just going to sing...
What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry, sorry...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm going to apologize.
Oh, my God.
Let me concentrate one more time!
Come on!
Oh, my God.
That's a long time.
That's a really long time.
Oh, bunk!
Oh, it's a tie, it's a tie.
All right!
Eh, you just ended the game!
Boring.
What are you gonna do? Jumping?
Wait a minute, booby prize.
Boo-boo, Aloha is the one who made this game, and he made it so we could play overtime and pk, but he didn't make it.
But he didn't make it.
He was afraid that he might lose,
He was afraid that I might beat him, so he didn't make it.
In other words,
I mean, he was the loser.
But I'll tell you one thing about that.
First of all, you don't win because there's a tie.
tied, so you didn't win.
I don't get it.
I don't know what I'm talking about either.
Next.
Can you just decide on the first half?
Wait a minute.
Okay.
That's it.
Let's not do that.
So we play one more game, the first half only.
Six minutes to decide.
My life?
My life is in six minutes?
It's the time limit of my life.
Oh, man, I'm serious. I'm really serious.
I haven't done anything wrong lately.
Seriously, I only cross at traffic lights.
I'm not at my best at times like this.
If I'm this timid before the game starts, I'm gonna lose.
Don't you think?
It's a ruse.
You have to give your opponent some leeway.
Then, when a goal is scored, that margin will be shattered.
It's the beginning of the truth.
Well...
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Hey, that's not fair!
You only have the ball for the first half of the game.
Give me the ball back.
You got it, didn't you?
Good boy. - Good boy.
Oh, there you go...
Whoo! Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
father of meat and hair
really, really, really
Really, really...
Aloha fans will be really upset.
No, Aloha, they'll think you're not manly enough!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, shit! That was close.
Yeah!
How do you feel?
Eeeee!
Ehhhh!
Uh, hey.
How do you feel? Right now...
Hey.
I know you were spying on me, but I got the ball, and now I'm...
Hey. Hey.
Are you okay?
Hey, Senpai!
Hey, let's be nice for once.
It's only the first half.
Hey, wait a minute. Let's be nice for once.
Hey, seriously, really, really, really, really, really...
How do you feel? Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, really, really, really, really...
I'll get angry at anything. I'll do anything.
Hey, how do you feel?
Hey!
Oh, my God!
Aaaaah!
Ehhhh!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, how do you feel?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Yeah, like last time.
I was just thinking...
We've already won.
Well, it's 2-0.
Oh, my God.
Poor guy.
Hey, you know what?
It's fun.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Seasonal art!
Oh, God!
Aaah!
What? Oh, no.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, my God, I'm losing power.
Oh, that feels good.
Oh my God, I think I'm gonna lose power too.
Ohhhhh, does it feel that good now?
Ouch!
Oh my God.
Wait till you get to the two-stene bottle.
My partner!
What?
What? It stopped.
My partner!
What? What?
What? It's kind of big, isn't it?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think the caller just called.
I've already won.
What do you mean, "I've already won"?
I'll never know who you are.
Reversal!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ehhhhhh...
Where is that heterosexuality you were talking about?
Oh, uh, uh,
Huh?
Uh-huh.
This is starting to get really weird.
We won.
Congratulations.
Good job.
Oh, yeah, you're Scotts.
Good job, Scotts.
Good work, Mr. Scootz.
So you're sure you're paying for it?
What? I'm buying this for my team.
Aaaaahhh...
So we can already buy it.
Eeeee...
It's a glasses shop in Ginza.
Ginza?
Are you on your way to the Ginza ban?
Yes, I have an appointment.
You have an appointment?
Yes, I do.
Can you stop for a second?
Yes, sir.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Aaah!
Ow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Son of a bitch!
Aaah!
No!
Ow!
Aaah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Well, I really enjoyed today's shoot.
I hope to have another chance to do something like this.
I hope we will have another chance to do something like this again.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all again!
See you next week!
How do you feel?
Huh?
Mr. Yerba Mate, how do you feel?
Tell me.
Hey.
Hey, you there.
Oh, it's you.
I'm sorry, how do you feel?
It's stuck.
How do you feel?
Oh, my God.
I could be a super sprout right now.
I want to see it, I want to see it, I want to see it, I want to see it, I want to see it
I'd like to see it
Once you get used to it, I'll let you off the hook.
I didn't bring my wallet
Then go Saiyan instead.
Don't add hair.
If I messed up my hair, the makeup artist would be pissed.
You know what, you... don't do that.
I'm a decent person.
I can't do something that would bother the makeup artist.
Don't say "I won't" or something like that.
I'll go back to normal after super disclosure.
I put my life on the line for laughter.
I'm gonna want to do it.
I'll just go.
Go, go, go.
That hurt.
So, uh...
I want you to get the cheapest one.
The most expensive?
Okay.
But if you know anything about soccer...
Deciding a game in the first half...
It's ridiculous.
The second half.
There's more drama in the second half.
Why did you decide the game in the first half?
Well, Ginza's already decided.
We're here.
Thank you for watching.